

CONTACT ME AT

+33 6 95 27 98 79

cyril@dbyzero.com

cyrilalfaro.com

in @cyril.alfaro

SKILLS SUMMARY

•••• DevOps : Docker, Kubernetes, GitlabCl, Bare server, AWS

Frontend: VanillaJS, React, WebGL, Redux, ViewJS, Cordova

Backend: NodeJS, Python, PHP,
PostgreSQL, Redis, Cassandra

Framework: Laravel, Django, Express, CakePHP, Drupal

Network: LPWan, SSL, Rest, GraphQL, Traefik

•••• Project Management

•••• French, English

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

- Engineering degree in software development (2007) E-CML,
 Marseilles
- Two-year university degree in technology Network and telecom (2004) IUT Joseph Fourrier Grenoble
- High-School Diploma in scientific field (2002) Lycée Gustave Jaume Pierrelatte

CYRIL ALFARO

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a software engineer with a strong entrepreneurship experience. I masterised many framework and languages over my carreer. I developed and managed developers teams since 15 years. I love create, improve and resolv problems using my large set of compentencies.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Chief Technical Officer (3 years)

IoT Valley | Apr 2018 - present

- Accelerate many startups to scale from 0 to 1
- Develop with my team a Framework arround data and IoT to save many months of development for startups
- Create many "POCs" using internal platform to help IoT Valley partnership that sometimes leads to new startup

Chief Technical Officer (2 years)

Xtraball | Apr 2016 - Apr 2018

- Managed a team to build an open source CMS that easily create mobile apps for iOS, Android and Windows phone.
- Create brand new internal tools to help buisness and marketing teams.
- Help and animate a community arround product accross

Senior Fullstack developer - DevOPS (3 years)

IWD | Jun 2013 - Apr 2016

- Create brand new CI to deploy and manage version
- Create a software for luxurious and retail enterprise to manage their shops.
- Create a VR Software for immersive experiences on virtual shops

Freelance developer (12 years)

DIVISION BY ZERO | 2009 - now

- Create a ticketing event applications
- Create an application to manage teams and sites for construction industry
- Create many community website